Finding Aid for the Alumni Relations Collection
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Deceased Alumni
  - Henslee, Lipe (Box 2650, Folder 29)
  - Henslee, Thomas Carlos (Box 2650, Folder 30)
  - Hensley, Clarence McCline (Box 2650, Folder 31)
  - Hensley, William A. (Box 2650, Folder 32)
  - Henson, Samuel L. (Box 2650, Folder 33)
  - Herbert, Chesley Carlisle (Box 2650, Folder 34)
  - Herbert, D. O. (Box 2650, Folder 35)
  - Herbert, Rogers Nathaniel, Photo (Box 2650, Folder 36)
  - Herbert, Thomas Grigsby (Box 2650, Folder 37)
  - Herblin, Mel (Box 2650, Folder 38)
  - Hereford, Julia (Box 2650, Folder 39)
  - Heriges, Robert M. (Box 2650, Folder 40)
  - Herlong, Fletcher R. (Box 2650, Folder 41)
  - Hermes, William (Box 2650, Folder 42)
  - Herod, Jack (Box 2650, Folder 43)
  - Heron, Shirley T. (Box 2650, Folder 44)
  - Herrin, William Kennedy (Box 2650, Folder 45)
  - Herring, W. E. (Box 2650, Folder 46)
  - Herron, Frank, Photo (Box 2650, Folder 47)
  - Herron, Frank White (Box 2650, Folder 48)
  - Herron, Louise White (Box 2650, Folder 49)
  - Hervey, James Theodore (Box 2650, Folder 50)
  - Heslep, W. A., Photo (Box 2650, Folder 51)
  - Hester, John Thomas, Photo (Box 2650, Folder 52)
  - Hewes, Robert Edward, Photo (Box 2650, Folder 53)
  - Hewett, Vernon B. (Box 2650, Folder 54)
  - Hewgley, Charles W. (Box 2650, Folder 55)
  - Hewlett, James Howell (Box 2650, Folder 56)
  - Heymann, George Hershel (Box 2650, Folder 57)
  - Hibarger, Joseph R. (Box 2650, Folder 58)
  - Hibbett, John Allen (Box 2650, Folder 59)
  - Hibbett, John Johnston (Box 2650, Folder 60)
  - Hibbett, Sanders Emmett (Box 2650, Folder 61)
  - Hibbitt, Robert F. (Box 2650, Folder 62)
  - Hibbitts, William (Box 2650, Folder 63)
  - Hibbs, Russell Aubra (Box 2650, Folder 64)
  - Hickerson, Allan (Box 2650, Folder 65)
  - Hickey, Rufus Morgan (Box 2650, Folder 66)
  - Hickman, Ernest F. (Box 2650, Folder 67)
  - Hickman, Rodney Elmer (Box 2650, Folder 68)
  - Hicks, E. R. (Box 2650, Folder 69)
  - Hicks, G. P. (Box 2650, Folder 70)
  - Hicks, Gordon Davis (Box 2650, Folder 71)
  - Hicks, Herbert Arthur (Box 2650, Folder 72)
  - Hicks, John Harden (Box 2650, Folder 73)
  - Hicks, W. T. (Box 2650, Folder 74)
  - Hicks, William N. (Box 2650, Folder 75)
  - Hicks, William P. (Box 2650, Folder 76)
  - Higginson, George (Box 2650, Folder 77)
  - Higginson, William (Box 2650, Folder 78)
  - Higgs, M. F. (Box 2650, Folder 79)
  - Hight, George Washington (Box 2650, Folder 80)
  - Hightower, Emmett (Box 2650, Folder 81)
  - Hightower, Emmett Dysart, Photo (Box 2650, Folder 82)
  - Hightower, Lewis Henry (Box 2650, Folder 83)
  - Hilburn, Oscar Peace (Box 2650, Folder 84)
  - Hildebrand, James Bell (Box 2650, Folder 85)
  - Hildebrand, William Weaver (Box 2650, Folder 86)
  - Hilderbrand, Oliver Edwin (Box 2650, Folder 87)
  - Hill, Adolph B. (Box 2650, Folder 88)
  - Hill, Adolph Burge (Junior), Photo (Box 2650, Folder 89)
  - Hill, Alexander Stanton (Box 2650, Folder 90)
  - Hill, Benjamin Dunlap (Box 2650, Folder 91)
  - Hill, Edgar Garlic (Box 2650, Folder 92)
  - Hill, Edward Bibb (Box 2650, Folder 93)
  - Hill, Felix Robertson (Box 2650, Folder 94)
  - Hill, John Beck (Box 2650, Folder 95)
  - Hill, John McMurray (Box 2650, Folder 96)
  - Hill, John Page, Photo (Box 2650, Folder 97)
  - Hill, Joseph Lafayette (Box 2650, Folder 98)
  - Hill, Malcolm Carnes (Box 2650, Folder 99)
  - Hill, Marjorie Sue (Box 2650, Folder 100)
  - Hill, Nelson Page (Box 2650, Folder 101)
  - Hill, Phillip Brockett and Bessie Fite (Wife) (Box 2650, Folder 102)
  - Hill, Remus Daniel (Box 2650, Folder 103)
  - Hill, Robert R. (Box 2650, Folder 104)
  - Hill, Rogers Lee, Photo (Box 2650, Folder 105)
  - Hill, S. B. (Box 2650, Folder 106)
  - Hill, Thurman K. (Box 2650, Folder 107)
  - Hill, W. I. (Box 2650, Folder 108)
  - Hille, William Bernard (Box 2650, Folder 109)
  - Hillman, J. William (Box 2650, Folder 110)
  - Hiller, Hiram K. (Box 2650, Folder 111)
  - Hillhouse, John Louden (Box 2650, Folder 112)
  - Himebaugh, Lyle B. (Box 2650, Folder 113)
  - Hinde, Hubbard K. (Box 2650, Folder 114)
  - Hindman, Sims Seward (Box 2650, Folder 115)
  - Hines, Benjamin H. (Box 2650, Folder 116)
  - Hines, Bennett M. (Box 2650, Folder 117)
  - Hines, John Owen (Box 2650, Folder 118)
  - Hines, Richard Percy (Box 2650, Folder 119)
  - Hines, Stedman Holt (Box 2650, Folder 120)
  - Hinkle, Carl C., All-American Football Player (Box 2650, Folder 121)
  - Hinkle, David Edward (Box 2650, Folder 122)
  - Hinson, O. I. (Box 2650, Folder 123)
  - Hinton, Allan Francis (Box 2650, Folder 124)
  - Hinton, Halqua Eldon (Box 2650, Folder 125)
  - Hinton, Harold B., Photo (Box 2650, Folder 126)
  - Hinton, J. A. (Box 2650, Folder 127)
  - Hinton, Sterling B. (Box 2650, Folder 128)
  - Hipp, Miriam Coile Hutton (Mrs. Macon A. Hipp) (Box 2650, Folder 129)
  - Hipp, W. Frank (Box 2650, Folder 130)
  - Hirshman, Sam H. (Box 2650, Folder 131)
  - Hirsig, James W. (Box 2650, Folder 132)
  - Hisle, George Hamilton (Box 2650, Folder 133)
  - Hitch, James Wood (Box 2650, Folder 134)
  - Hite, Anne Gillespie (Box 2650, Folder 135)
  - Hite, Charles Maner, Photo (Box 2650, Folder 136)
  - Hite, Mary Kathryn Fink (Mrs. W. K. Hite) (Box 2650, Folder 137)
  - Hitt, Edward Franklin (Box 2650, Folder 138)
  - Hix, Sidney Dayton (Box 2650, Folder 139)
  - Hixon, Frank Petty (Box 2650, Folder 140)
  - Hoard, William Taylor (Box 2650, Folder 141)
  - Hobbie, Richard Martin (Box 2650, Folder 142)
  - Hobbs, Anna Russell Weaver Farrell (Mrs. Thomas Meredith Hobbs and Mrs. Herbert Farrell) (Box 2650, Folder 143)
  - Hobbs, Samuel Francis, United States Congressman (Alabama) (Box 2650, Folder 144)
  - Hobbs, Tarleton Craig (Box 2650, Folder 145)
  - Hobby, A. Worth, Photo (Box 2650, Folder 146)
  - Hobson, Joel Jones (Box 2650, Folder 147)
  - Hocker, John Wesley (Box 2650, Folder 148)
  - Hocker, Sam K. (Box 2650, Folder 149)
  - Hockett, John Cornelius (Box 2650, Folder 150)
  - Hodge, Z. T. (Box 2650, Folder 151)
  - Hodges, D. M. (Box 2650, Folder 152)
  - Hodges, Eldridge W. (Box 2650, Folder 153)
  - Hodges, W. A. (Box 2650, Folder 154)
  - Hodges, Wilbur Dexter (Box 2650, Folder 155)
  - Hodgins, Thomas E. (Box 2650, Folder 156)
  - Hodsdon, Carroll Tracy (Box 2650, Folder 157)
  - Hoepfner, Theodore Christian (Box 2650, Folder 158)
  - Hoffer, Carl W., Photo (Box 2650, Folder 159)
  - Hogan, Earl Aden (Box 2650, Folder 160)
  - Hogan, Francis Woodall, Photo (Box 2650, Folder 161)
  - Hogan, John Harris (Box 2650, Folder 162)
  - Hogg, William Bennett (Box 2650, Folder 163)
  - Hogg, William F. (Box 2650, Folder 164)
  - Hoggins, Paul W. (Box 2650, Folder 165)
  - Hogue, James E. (Box 2650, Folder 166)
  - Hohlfeld, Alexander R. (Box 2650, Folder 167)
  - Holcomb, Numa Ried, Missouri State Representative (Box 2650, Folder 168)
  - Holcombe, Armistead R. (Box 2650, Folder 169)
  - Holder, Harry A. (Box 2650, Folder 170)
  - Holder, James Fred, Photo (Box 2650, Folder 171)
  - Holderness, James S. (Box 2650, Folder 172)
  - Holderness, Marvin Early and Eunice B. Jackson (Wife), Photo (Box 2650, Folder 173)
  - Holderness, Marvin Early (Junior), Photo (Box 2651, Folder 1)
  - Holdsworth, Jeral Rea (Box 2651, Folder 2)
  - Hollabaugh, Andrew Newton (Box 2651, Folder 3)
  - Hollabaugh, Andrew Newton (Junior) (Box 2651, Folder 4)
  - Hollabaugh, Cleveland Buchanan (Box 2651, Folder 5)
  - Hollabaugh, Mrs. Cleveland Buchanan (Box 2651, Folder 6)
  - Holladay, John Denny (Box 2651, Folder 7)
  - Holland, Eugene Fletcher (Box 2651, Folder 8)
  - Holland, James Leland and Ernestine Graves (Wife), Photo (Box 2651, Folder 9)
  - Holland, John Warthen (Box 2651, Folder 10)
  - Holland, Richard Marion (Box 2651, Folder 11)
  - Holland, William Cannon and Jane Medearis (Wife) (Box 2651, Folder 12)
  - Holley, A. R. (Box 2651, Folder 13)
  - Hollingsworth, James Isbin (Box 2651, Folder 14)
  - Hollins, Edwin Charles (Box 2651, Folder 15)
  - Hollins, Eugene Thompson, Photo (Box 2651, Folder 16)
  - Hollins, Lunsford Meredith (Box 2651, Folder 17)
  - Hollinshead, Russell Pitt (Box 2651, Folder 18)
  - Hollinshead, Warren Henry and Margaret B. Roberson (Wife), Photo (Box 2651, Folder 19)
  - Holloran, James Edward (Box 2651, Folder 20)
  - Holman, D. Wilson (Box 2651, Folder 21)
  - Holman, Harry Thomas (Box 2651, Folder 22)
  - Holman, James Wilson (Box 2651, Folder 23)
  - Holman, Joe W. (Box 2651, Folder 24)
  - Holman, John Daniel, Photo (Box 2651, Folder 25)
  - Holman, Russell Lowell (Box 2651, Folder 26)
  - Holman, William Franklin (Box 2651, Folder 27)
  - Holmes, Albert Earle (Box 2651, Folder 28)
  - Holmes, Andrew Owens, Photo; Tennessee State Supreme Court Justice (Box 2651, Folder 29)
  - Holmes, Francis (Box 2651, Folder 30)
  - Holmes, George M. (Box 2651, Folder 31)
  - Holmes, John G. (Box 2651, Folder 32)
  - Holmes, John Parham, Photo (Box 2651, Folder 33)
  - Holmes, Katherine A. (Box 2651, Folder 34)
  - Holmes, Louise Lenoir (Box 2651, Folder 35)
  - Holmes, Lysander Plamer (Box 2651, Folder 36)
  - Holmes, Roy Jones (Box 2651, Folder 37)
  - Holmes, Thomas Wilburn (Box 2651, Folder 38)
  - Holmes, William Walter (Box 2651, Folder 39)
  - Holmsley, Francis Marion (Box 2651, Folder 40)
  - Holsinger, Amos Stover Alvis (Box 2651, Folder 41)
  - Holt, Cecil Rupert (Box 2651, Folder 42)
  - Holt, Chester P., Photo (Box 2651, Folder 43)
  - Holt, David D. (Box 2651, Folder 44)
  - Holt, George Edward (Box 2651, Folder 45)
  - Holt, Ivan Lee, Photo (Box 2651, Folder 46)
  - Holt, James L. (Box 2651, Folder 47)
  - Holt, John Broadus, Photo (Box 2651, Folder 48)
  - Holt, Parker (Folder 1 of 2), Photo (Box 2651, Folder 49)
  - Holt, Parker (Folder 2 of 2), Photo (Box 2651, Folder 50)
  - Holt, Richard Bryan, Photo (Box 2651, Folder 51)
  - Holt, Robert Earl (Box 2651, Folder 52)
  - Holt, Rufus Leroy (Box 2651, Folder 53)
  - Holt, Verna (Box 2651, Folder 54)
  - Holt, William Fisher, Photo (Box 2651, Folder 55)
  - Hood, Ernest James (Box 2651, Folder 56)
  - Hood, Frederick B. (Box 2651, Folder 57)
  - Hooper, Warner (Box 2651, Folder 58)
  - Hooten, Carney Lipscomb (Box 2651, Folder 59)
  - Hoover, Everett Bell (Box 2651, Folder 60)
  - Hopkins, Arvah St. Clair (Box 2651, Folder 61)
  - Hopkins, George Thomas (Box 2651, Folder 62)
  - Hopkins, John M. (Box 2651, Folder 63)
  - Hopkins, John W. (Box 2651, Folder 64)
  - Hopkins, Harry Panton (Box 2651, Folder 65)
  - Hopkins, Hinton John (Box 2651, Folder 66)
  - Hopkins, Lenoard Otis (Box 2651, Folder 67)
  - Hopkins, Manly Ross (Box 2651, Folder 68)
  - Hopkins, Percy Isaiah (Box 2651, Folder 69)
  - Hopkinson, Margaret Lamb (Mrs. Frederick James Hopkinson) (Box 2651, Folder 70)
  - Hopper, Mary Elizabeth Corley (Mrs. Clarence Franklin Hopper) (Box 2651, Folder 71)
  - Hopps, Emery O. (Box 2651, Folder 72)
  - Horan, Ralph W., Oregon State Legislator (Box 2651, Folder 73)
  - Horn, Abraham Edward (Box 2651, Folder 74)
  - Horn, George Harding (Box 2651, Folder 75)
  - Hornaday, Charles Edwin and Marjorie Loggins (Wife), Photo (Box 2651, Folder 76)
  - Hornback, J. M. (Box 2651, Folder 77)
  - Horne, William D. (Box 2651, Folder 78)
  - Horner, Buford Bernard (Box 2651, Folder 79)
  - Horner, Claude Sullivan (Box 2651, Folder 80)
  - Horsley, Robert H. (Box 2651, Folder 81)
  - Horton, Everett Victor (Box 2651, Folder 82)
  - Horton, John Wiloite (Box 2651, Folder 83)
  - Horton, Joseph W. (Box 2651, Folder 84)
  - Hoskins, J. Milton (Box 2651, Folder 85)
  - Hoskins, John S. (Box 2651, Folder 86)
  - Hoskins, T. M. (Box 2651, Folder 87)
  - Hounshell, Charles Gideon (Box 2651, Folder 88)
  - House, Caroline W. Carpenter (Mrs. I. S. House) (Box 2651, Folder 89)
  - House, Samuel John (Box 2651, Folder 90)
  - House, William Carl (Box 2651, Folder 91)
  - Housman, William Hardy (Box 2651, Folder 92)
  - Houston, Dick Frank (Box 2651, Folder 93)
  - Houston, Edward Cyrus (Box 2651, Folder 94)
  - Houston, Hal Edward and Adelaide L. Eubanks (Wife) (Box 2651, Folder 95)
  - Houston, Henry Milton (Box 2651, Folder 96)
  - Houston, James L. (Box 2651, Folder 97)
  - Houston, Matt Francis (Box 2651, Folder 98)
  - Houston, Persis Daniel (Board of Trust Member), Photo (Box 2651, Folder 99)
  - Houston, Richard Robinson (Robert or Bobby) (Box 2651, Folder 100)
  - Houston, Simpson Fugett (Box 2651, Folder 101)
  - Houston, Trim (Box 2651, Folder 102)
  - Houston, William Cyrus (Box 2651, Folder 103)
  - Howard, Alexnder Travis (Box 2651, Folder 104)
  - Howard, Allan H., Photo (Box 2651, Folder 105)
  - Howard, Ben Victor (Box 2651, Folder 106)
  - Howard, Clarence Henry, Photo (Box 2651, Folder 107)
  - Howard, Eugene Rice (Box 2651, Folder 108)
  - Howard, John B. (Box 2651, Folder 109)
  - Howard, Lawrence Branch, Photo (Box 2651, Folder 110)
  - Howard, William Harris (Box 2651, Folder 111)
  - Howard, William James (Box 2651, Folder 112)
  - Howard, Willis T. (Box 2651, Folder 113)
  - Howe, Beverly Winslow (Box 2651, Folder 114)
  - Howe, Elizabeth Patton (Betsy) (Box 2651, Folder 115)
  - Howe, John Bond Atkinson (Box 2651, Folder 116)
  - Howe, Thomas Patterson (Box 2651, Folder 117)
  - Howe, William H. (Box 2651, Folder 118)
  - Howe, William P. (Box 2651, Folder 119)
  - Howell, Alfred Elliott (Box 2651, Folder 120)
  - Howell, Barbara Ann (Box 2651, Folder 121)
  - Howell, Evan C., Photo (Box 2651, Folder 122)
  - Howell, Gertie Lee Nannie (Mrs. James O. Howell) (Box 2651, Folder 123)
  - Howell, Helen M. (Box 2651, Folder 124)
  - Howell, Joseph Toy, Photo (Box 2651, Folder 125)
  - Howell, John Blanch (Box 2651, Folder 126)
  - Howell, John Blanch (Junior) (Box 2651, Folder 127)
  - Howell, Mamie Craig (Mrs. Joseph Toy Howell) (Box 2651, Folder 128)
  - Howell, Morton Boyte (Box 2651, Folder 129)
  - Howell, Morton Boyte (III), Photo (Box 2651, Folder 130)
  - Howell, R. Boyte C. (Box 2651, Folder 131)
  - Howell, R. Boyte C. (Junior) (Box 2651, Folder 132)
  - Howington, James Timothy (Box 2652, Folder 1)
  - Howland, John Stapleton (Box 2652, Folder 2)
  - Howlett, Kirby Smith (Box 2652, Folder 3)
  - Howorth, Joseph Robert (Box 2652, Folder 5)
  - Howser, Fred (Box 2652, Folder 6)
  - Howser, Louis Francis (Box 2652, Folder 7)
  - Howser, Stephen Nichols (Box 2652, Folder 8)
  - Hoye, Matthew John Lucas (Box 2652, Folder 9)
  - Hruska, Ralph E. (Box 2652, Folder 10)
  - Hsieh, Daniel C. W. (Daniel Z. V. Zia) (Box 2652, Folder 11)
  - Huang, Jen-Lin, Photo; Chiang Kai-shek Confidante (Box 2652, Folder 12)
  - Hubbard, Elizabeth Simpson (Mrs. Wilder Walton Hubbard) (Box 2652, Folder 13)
  - Hubbard, George W., Meharry Medical College Founder (Box 2652, Folder 14)
  - Hubbard, Wilder Walton (William) (Box 2652, Folder 15)
  - Huckaby, William Ramsey (Buddy) (Box 2652, Folder 16)
  - Huddleston, Alfred Blackman (Box 2652, Folder 17)
  - Huddleston, G. D. (Box 2652, Folder 18)
  - Huddleston, Hal W., Photo (Box 2652, Folder 19)
  - Huddleston, William Thomas (Box 2652, Folder 20)
  - Hudgens, Robert H. (Box 2652, Folder 21)
  - Hudgins, Paul Grainger (Box 2652, Folder 22)
  - Hudgins, Ward (Box 2652, Folder 23)
  - Hudson, Alberto (Box 2652, Folder 24)
  - Hudson, Charles Mell (Box 2652, Folder 25)
  - Hudson, Grandville W. (Box 2652, Folder 26)
  - Hudson, Irby Roland, Photo (Box 2652, Folder 27)
  - Hudson, J. R. (Box 2652, Folder 28)
  - Hudson, James Irwin Hamilton, Photo (Box 2652, Folder 29)
  - Hudson, K. E. (Box 2652, Folder 30)
  - Hudson, Laurence Doyle (Box 2652, Folder 31)
  - Hudson, Millard Filmore, Photo (Box 2652, Folder 32)
  - Hudson, Richard Hall (Box 2652, Folder 33)
  - Hudson, Robert Dade (Box 2652, Folder 34)
  - Hudson, Samuel Edward (Box 2652, Folder 35)
  - Hudson, Thomas M. (Box 2652, Folder 36)
  - Hudson, Washington E. (Box 2652, Folder 37)
  - Hudspeth, Preston Southern (Box 2652, Folder 38)
  - Huey, Thomas Ford (Box 2652, Folder 39)
  - Huff, A. LeRoy (Box 2652, Folder 40)
  - Huff, Isabelle (Box 2652, Folder 41)
  - Huff, Rebecca Greer (Box 2652, Folder 42)
  - Huff, William Tipton (Box 2652, Folder 43)
  - Huffaker, Ebenezer (Box 2652, Folder 44)
  - Huffaker, Robert Olin (Box 2652, Folder 45)
  - Huffine, Thomas A. (Box 2652, Folder 46)
  - Huffman, Charles C. (Box 2652, Folder 47)
  - Huffman, Harold Funston (Box 2652, Folder 48)
  - Huffman, W. A. Hooper (Box 2652, Folder 49)
  - Huffman, William Edward (Box 2652, Folder 50)
  - Huffstutler, John Terry, Photo (Box 2652, Folder 51)
  - Huggins, David S. (Box 2652, Folder 52)
  - Huggins, James I. (Box 2652, Folder 53)
  - Huggins, William P. (Peck) (Box 2652, Folder 54)
  - Huggins, William S. (Box 2652, Folder 55)
  - Hughes, Edwin Cutter (Box 2652, Folder 56)
  - Hughes, Frank B. (Box 2652, Folder 57)
  - Hughes, George A. (Box 2652, Folder 58)
  - Hughes, George Taylor (Box 2652, Folder 59)
  - Hughes, Georgene (Box 2652, Folder 60)
  - Hughes, Hardin Ivan (Box 2652, Folder 61)
  - Hughes, H. B. (Box 2652, Folder 62)
  - Hughes, John Wesley (Box 2652, Folder 63)
  - Hughes, Leonard B. (Box 2652, Folder 64)
  - Hughes, M. L. (Box 2652, Folder 65)
  - Hughes, Maurice Byron (Box 2652, Folder 66)
  - Hughes, Miles Preston (Box 2652, Folder 67)
  - Hughes, Nat Cheaires (Box 2652, Folder 68)
  - Hughes, Richard Hartwell (Box 2652, Folder 69)
  - Hughes, Russell Houston (Box 2652, Folder 70)
  - Hughes, Shelly G. (Box 2652, Folder 71)
  - Hughes, Thomas Allen (Box 2652, Folder 72)
  - Hughes, Thomas Allen (Junior) (Box 2652, Folder 73)
  - Hughes, William (Board of Trust Member), Photo (Box 2652, Folder 74)
  - Hughes, William Wightman (Box 2652, Folder 75)
  - Hughey, Allen Harrison, Photo (Box 2652, Folder 76)
  - Hughey, James Monroe (Box 2652, Folder 77)
  - Hull, Angus Clifton (Box 2652, Folder 78)
  - Hull, Charles Henry, Photo (Box 2652, Folder 79)
  - Hull, Dabney Herndon (Box 2652, Folder 80)
  - Hull, Horace Hobson (Box 2652, Folder 81)
  - Hull, Marvin Ross (Box 2652, Folder 82)
  - Hull, William Quillian (Box 2652, Folder 83)
  - Hulme, Fountain Bruce (Box 2652, Folder 84)
  - Hulme, William Henry (Box 2652, Folder 85)
  - Hulsey, William Noble (Box 2652, Folder 86)
  - Hultsman, St. Clair, Photo (Box 2652, Folder 87)
  - Humbert, Walter Cowden (Box 2652, Folder 88)
  - Hume, Alfred, Photo; Chancellor of University of Mississippi (Box 2652, Folder 89)
  - Hume, Foster (Box 2652, Folder 91)
  - Hume, Fred, Photo (Box 2652, Folder 92)
  - Hume, Fred (Junior) (Box 2653, Folder 1)
  - Hume, James Porter (Box 2653, Folder 2)
  - Hume, Leland (Box 2653, Folder 3)
  - Hume, Mayes (Box 2653, Folder 4)
  - Hume, Sallie M. (Box 2653, Folder 5)
  - Hume, William (Box 2653, Folder 6)
  - Hume, William Bradford (Box 2653, Folder 7)
  - Humphrey, Howard McKenzie, Photo (Box 2653, Folder 8)
  - Humphries, Eugene Percy (Box 2653, Folder 9)
  - Hundley, Oscar Richard, Photo (Box 2653, Folder 10)
  - Hunnicutt, Emily (Box 2653, Folder 11)
  - Hunnicutt, Wilbur Littleton (Box 2653, Folder 12)
  - Hunt, Albert Clarence, Photo; Oklahoma State Supreme Court Justice (Box 2653, Folder 13)
  - Hunt, Alvin Morris (Box 2653, Folder 14)
  - Hunt, Clarence Martin (Box 2653, Folder 15)
  - Hunt, Douglas L. (Box 2653, Folder 16)
  - Hunt, Edwin Francis and Katherine Flinn (Wife), Photo (Box 2653, Folder 17)
  - Hunt, Evelyn Berry Wyker (Mrs. F. S. Hunt) (Box 2653, Folder 18)
  - Hunt, Henry Franklin (Box 2653, Folder 19)
  - Hunt, Herbert Hobson (Box 2653, Folder 20)
  - Hunt, Jasper Stewart and Anne Wright (Wife) (Box 2653, Folder 21)
  - Hunt, Julian Roche (Box 2653, Folder 22)
  - Hunt, Kenneth Stovall (Box 2653, Folder 23)
  - Hunt, Noel Clarence (Box 2653, Folder 24)
  - Hunt, Samuel (Box 2653, Folder 25)
  - Hunt, Sidney Jackson (Box 2653, Folder 26)
  - Hunt, William James, Photo (Box 2653, Folder 27)
  - Hunt, William Roy (Box 2653, Folder 28)
  - Hunter, Alexander V. (Box 2653, Folder 29)
  - Hunter, Benbury W. (Box 2653, Folder 30)
  - Hunter, Edward Marshall (Box 2653, Folder 31)
  - Hunter, Eugene Griggs (Box 2653, Folder 32)
  - Hunter, Floyd Turner (Box 2653, Folder 33)
  - Hunter, Frank Whitfield (Box 2653, Folder 34)
  - Hunter, Harrison B. (Box 2653, Folder 35)
  - Hunter, J. R. (Box 2653, Folder 36)
  - Hunter, James Duncan (Box 2653, Folder 37)
  - Hunter, James Duncan (Junior) (Box 2653, Folder 38)
  - Hunter, John Henry (Box 2653, Folder 39)
  - Hunter, Joseph Howell (Box 2653, Folder 40)
  - Hunter, Paul and Emily Lambert Davis (Wife) (Box 2653, Folder 41)
  - Hunter, Ripley H. (Box 2653, Folder 42)
  - Hunter, Wright (Box 2653, Folder 43)
  - Hurst, Mary Elizabeth Thompson (Mrs. Andrew W. Hurst) (Box 2653, Folder 44)
  - Hurst, Sarah Clark Coston (Mrs. George B. Hurst) (Box 2653, Folder 45)
  - Hurt, Arthur Raymond (Box 2653, Folder 46)
  - Hurt, James William (Box 2653, Folder 47)
  - Hurt, John Briggs (Box 2653, Folder 48)
  - Hurt, John Harrison (Box 2653, Folder 49)
  - Hurt, S. M. R. (Box 2653, Folder 50)
  - Husband, William G. (Box 2653, Folder 51)
  - Hussey, John H. (Box 2653, Folder 52)
  - Hussey, Paul Edward (Box 2653, Folder 53)
  - Hust, Reuben L. (Box 2653, Folder 54)
  - Hutcherson, John Pinkney (Box 2653, Folder 55)
  - Hutcheson, William Gilmer (Box 2653, Folder 56)
  - Hutcheson, William Gilmer (Junior - Ax 1915) (Box 2653, Folder 57)
  - Hutcheson, William Gilmer (Junior - AcaEx 1936) (Box 2653, Folder 58)
  - Hutchings, Edgar Powell (Box 2653, Folder 59)
  - Hutchings, Norman Webb, Photo (Box 2653, Folder 60)
  - Hutchinson, Dudley Isom (Box 2653, Folder 61)
  - Hutchinson, Forney (Box 2653, Folder 62)
  - Hutchison, John Luther (Box 2653, Folder 63)
  - Hutchison, Walter George (Box 2653, Folder 64)
  - Hutchison, William Turner (Box 2653, Folder 65)
  - Hutson, Isabelle Blake Coles (Mrs. Hutson) (Box 2653, Folder 66)
  - Hutto, David Nixon, Photo (Box 2653, Folder 67)
  - Hutton, Clake Holman (Box 2653, Folder 68)
  - Hutton, John Walter (Box 2653, Folder 69)
  - Hutton, Major Ernest (Box 2653, Folder 70)
  - Hutton, Thomas Carlyle (Box 2653, Folder 71)
  - Hutton, William Taylor and Nancy Stone (Wife) (Box 2653, Folder 72)
  - Hux, O. M. (Box 2653, Folder 73)
  - Hux, William Jackson (Box 2653, Folder 74)
  - Hyatt, James Lee (Box 2653, Folder 75)
  - Hyatt, James Philip (Box 2653, Folder 76)
  - Hyde, Dorris Wilbur, Photo (Box 2653, Folder 77)
  - Hyde, Freeman Jordan (Box 2653, Folder 78)
  - Hyde, Hartwell Blount, Photo (Box 2653, Folder 79)
  - Hyde, I. N. (Box 2653, Folder 80)
  - Hyde, Thomas Jennings (Box 2653, Folder 81)
  - Hyde, Walter Horton (Box 2653, Folder 82)
  - Hyder, R. Bennick (Box 2653, Folder 83)
  - Hydrick, Daniel Edward, Photo (Box 2653, Folder 84)
  - Hyman, Leonard and Civia Olshine (Wife) (Box 2653, Folder 85)
  - Hyman, Maurice (Box 2653, Folder 86)
  - Hymel, Josephine Finney (Mrs. G. J. Hymel) (Box 2653, Folder 87)
  - Hynds, John Arthur (Box 2653, Folder 88)
  - Hyslop, Leland F. (Box 2653, Folder 89)
  - Ikard, Joseph Orville (Box 2653, Folder 90)
  - Ikard, William Elija (Box 2653, Folder 91)
  - Iles, Thomas J. (Thomas Iles Pegram) (Box 2653, Folder 92)
  - Iling, Leo M. (Box 2653, Folder 93)
  - Ingersoll, Robert Joseph (Box 2653, Folder 94)
  - Ingerson, C. Dudley (Box 2653, Folder 95)
  - Inglis, Edgar Auchincloss (Box 2653, Folder 96)
  - Ingram, John Jay (Box 2653, Folder 97)
  - Ingram, M. Dee (Box 2653, Folder 98)
  - Ingram, Thomas Harkins (Box 2653, Folder 99)
  - Irby, Alfred (Box 2653, Folder 100)
  - Irby, John Poindexter (Box 2653, Folder 101)
  - Ireland, Charles Byron (Box 2653, Folder 102)
  - Ireland, William Wesley (Box 2653, Folder 103)
  - Irion, J. W., Photo (Box 2653, Folder 104)
  - Irish, Alva Richards (Box 2653, Folder 105)
  - Irvin, Robert E. D. (Box 2653, Folder 106)
  - Irvine, William Gilmer (Box 2653, Folder 107)
  - Irwin, Gladys C. (Box 2653, Folder 108)
  - Isbell, Robert Godfrey (See Robert Gold Isbell) (Box 2653, Folder 109)